[
    [
        {
            "question": "Eye is modeled as a refracting surface. Distance from surface for focus is:",
            "options": [
                "3.1 cm",
                "4.0 cm",
                "1 cm",
                "2 cm"
            ],
            "correctOption": "3.1 cm",
            "id": 33
        },
        {
            "question": "Four particles A, B, C, D have same momentum. Which has max kinetic energy?",
            "options": [
                "D",
                "C",
                "A",
                "B"
            ],
            "correctOption": "A",
            "id": 4
        },
        {
            "question": "Phase difference between alternating current and emf is \u03c0/2. Not in circuit?",
            "options": [
                "LC",
                "L alone",
                "C alone",
                "R, L"
            ],
            "correctOption": "R, L",
            "id": 45
        },
        {
            "question": "As the beam enters the medium, it will:",
            "options": [
                "travel as a cylindrical beam",
                "converge",
                "diverge",
                "diverge near axis and converge at periphery"
            ],
            "correctOption": "converge",
            "id": 32
        },
        {
            "question": "A charged particle enters a magnetic field perpendicular to its velocity. The path of the particle is:",
            "options": [
                "Circular",
                "Linear",
                "Parabolic",
                "Elliptical"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Circular",
            "id": 47
        },
        {
            "question": "A long straight wire carries a current of 10 A. The magnetic field at a distance of 2 cm from the wire is:",
            "options": [
                "1 \u00d7 10\u207b\u2075 T",
                "10\u207b\u2076 T",
                "1 \u00d7 10\u207b\u2074 T",
                "10\u207b\u2077 T"
            ],
            "correctOption": "1 \u00d7 10\u207b\u2074 T",
            "id": 46
        },
        {
            "question": "The speed of light in the medium is:",
            "options": [
                "minimum on the axis of the beam",
                "maximum on the axis of the beam",
                "the same everywhere in the beam",
                "directly proportional to the intensity I"
            ],
            "correctOption": "minimum on the axis of the beam",
            "id": 31
        },
        {
            "question": "Fundamental frequency of a closed pipe = first overtone of open pipe. If open pipe is 60 cm, closed pipe is:",
            "options": [
                "15",
                "20",
                "25",
                "60"
            ],
            "correctOption": "15",
            "id": 16
        },
        {
            "question": "Average KE of a monatomic molecule is 0.414 eV. Temp is:",
            "options": [
                "3000 K",
                "3200 K",
                "1600 K",
                "1500 K"
            ],
            "correctOption": "3200 K",
            "id": 12
        },
        {
            "question": "Two satellites A and B in same orbit. A is twice mass of B. Which is same for both?",
            "options": [
                "Potential energy",
                "Total energy",
                "Kinetic energy",
                "Speed"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Speed",
            "id": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "A vector of magnitude 10 units makes an angle of 60\u00b0 with the x-axis. Its y-component is:",
            "options": [
                "10\u221a3/2",
                "10/2",
                "5\u221a3",
                "5"
            ],
            "correctOption": "10\u221a3/2",
            "id": 22
        },
        {
            "question": "Red LED emits 0.1W uniformly. Electric field amplitude at 1 m is:",
            "options": [
                "2.45 V/m",
                "7.75 V/m",
                "1.73 V/m",
                "5.48 V/m"
            ],
            "correctOption": "2.45 V/m",
            "id": 43
        },
        {
            "question": "AC cannot be measured by DC ammeter because:",
            "options": [
                "A.C cannot pass",
                "A.C changes direction",
                "Avg value is zero",
                "D.C. ammeter gets damaged"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Avg value is zero",
            "id": 44
        },
        {
            "question": "Two forces A and A/2 are perpendicular. Resultant magnitude is:",
            "options": [
                "(\u221a5)A/2",
                "5A/2",
                "(\u221a5)A\u00b2/2",
                "(\u221a5)A/4"
            ],
            "correctOption": "(\u221a5)A/2",
            "id": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Work function is 4.0 eV. Longest wavelength to emit photoelectrons is:",
            "options": [
                "540 nm",
                "400 nm",
                "310 nm",
                "220 nm"
            ],
            "correctOption": "310 nm",
            "id": 39
        },
        {
            "question": "Weight of a body on Earth is 400 N. At half Earth's radius depth, it will be:",
            "options": [
                "200 N",
                "300 N",
                "100 N",
                "Zero"
            ],
            "correctOption": "200 N",
            "id": 6
        },
        {
            "question": "A car accelerates uniformly from rest and covers a distance of 100 m in 5 s. Its acceleration is:",
            "options": [
                "8 m/s\u00b2",
                "10 m/s\u00b2",
                "5 m/s\u00b2",
                "6 m/s\u00b2"
            ],
            "correctOption": "8 m/s\u00b2",
            "id": 21
        },
        {
            "question": "The dimensional formula for pressure is:",
            "options": [
                "ML\u207b\u00b9T\u207b\u00b2",
                "MLT\u207b\u00b2",
                "ML\u00b2T\u207b\u00b2",
                "M\u207b\u00b9L\u207b\u00b9T\u207b\u00b2"
            ],
            "correctOption": "ML\u207b\u00b9T\u207b\u00b2",
            "id": 23
        },
        {
            "question": "Two projectiles A and B are thrown at 40 m/s and 60 m/s at angles 30\u00b0 and 60\u00b0. The ratio of their ranges is:",
            "options": [
                "4 : 9",
                "2 : 3",
                "1 : 1",
                "3 : 2"
            ],
            "correctOption": "4 : 9",
            "id": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "In an LCR series circuit, the resonance frequency is given by:",
            "options": [
                "1/(2\u03c0\u221a(LC))",
                "1/(2\u03c0RC)",
                "1/(2\u03c0LR)",
                "1/(LC)"
            ],
            "correctOption": "1/(2\u03c0\u221a(LC))",
            "id": 48
        },
        {
            "question": "A capacitor of 9 pF is filled with two dielectrics (k1 = 3, k2 = 6). The new capacitance is:",
            "options": [
                "20.25 pF",
                "1.8 pF",
                "45 pF",
                "40.5 pF"
            ],
            "correctOption": "40.5 pF",
            "id": 30
        },
        {
            "question": "Radioactive source gives 1600 cps at t=0, 100 cps at t=8s. At t=6s it gives:",
            "options": [
                "250",
                "360",
                "150",
                "200"
            ],
            "correctOption": "200",
            "id": 40
        },
        {
            "question": "In SHM, if displacement is half amplitude, ratio of PE to KE is:",
            "options": [
                "1:1",
                "1:4",
                "2:1",
                "1:3"
            ],
            "correctOption": "1:3",
            "id": 20
        },
        {
            "question": "In Young\u2019s experiment, path difference is (\u215b)\u03bb. Intensity ratio to central fringe is:",
            "options": [
                "0.80",
                "0.94",
                "0.85",
                "0.74"
            ],
            "correctOption": "0.85",
            "id": 34
        },
        {
            "question": "Needles of ferro-, para- and diamagnetic materials react to magnet by:",
            "options": [
                "attract N1 strongly, N2 weakly and repel N3 weakly",
                "attract all three",
                "attract N1 and N2 strongly but repel N3",
                "attract N1 strongly, but repel N2 and N3 weakly"
            ],
            "correctOption": "attract N1 strongly, N2 weakly and repel N3 weakly",
            "id": 41
        },
        {
            "question": "A particle of mass 500 g has velocity (2t i + 3t\u00b2 j) m/s. Force at t=1s is (i + xj). Find x:",
            "options": [
                "4",
                "3",
                "6",
                "2"
            ],
            "correctOption": "3",
            "id": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Engine between boiling and freezing points of water. Efficiency:",
            "options": [
                "2, 3 and 4 only",
                "2 and 3 only",
                "2 and 4 only",
                "1 and 2 only"
            ],
            "correctOption": "2 and 4 only",
            "id": 14
        },
        {
            "question": "The energy of a photon is 3.3 \u00d7 10\u207b\u00b9\u2079 J. Its frequency is (Planck's constant h = 6.626 \u00d7 10\u207b\u00b3\u2074 Js):",
            "options": [
                "5 \u00d7 10\u00b9\u2074 Hz",
                "3 \u00d7 10\u2078 Hz",
                "2 \u00d7 10\u00b9\u2074 Hz",
                "1 \u00d7 10\u2079 Hz"
            ],
            "correctOption": "5 \u00d7 10\u00b9\u2074 Hz",
            "id": 50
        },
        {
            "question": "The moment of inertia of a solid sphere about its diameter is:",
            "options": [
                "2/5 MR\u00b2",
                "3/5 MR\u00b2",
                "1/2 MR\u00b2",
                "2/3 MR\u00b2"
            ],
            "correctOption": "2/5 MR\u00b2",
            "id": 24
        },
        {
            "question": "A solid conducting sphere with charge Q is surrounded by an uncharged conducting hollow shell. If shell is given charge \u20134Q, the new potential difference is:",
            "options": [
                "4 V",
                "V",
                "2 V",
                "\u20132 V"
            ],
            "correctOption": "V",
            "id": 27
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "Statement I: Fluorine has most negative electron gain enthalpy in its group. Statement II: Oxygen has least negative electron gain enthalpy in its group.",
            "options": [
                "BOTH I AND II ARE TRUE",
                "BOTH I AND II ARE FALSE",
                "I IS TRUE BUT II IS FALSE",
                "II IS TRUE BUT I IS FALSE"
            ],
            "correctOption": "II IS TRUE BUT I IS FALSE",
            "id": 40
        },
        {
            "question": "Determine the total number of neutrons in three isotopes of hydrogen",
            "options": [
                "1",
                "2",
                "3",
                "4"
            ],
            "correctOption": "3",
            "id": 29
        },
        {
            "question": "Addition of phosphate fertilizers to water bodies causes",
            "options": [
                "enhanced growth of algae",
                "increase in amount of dissolved oxygen in water",
                "deposition of calcium phosphate",
                "increase in fish population"
            ],
            "correctOption": "enhanced growth of algae",
            "id": 28
        },
        {
            "question": "Which one of the following conformation of cyclohexane is chiral?",
            "options": [
                "Twist boat",
                "Rigid",
                "Chair",
                "Boat"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Twist boat",
            "id": 23
        },
        {
            "question": "The incorrect statements regarding enzymes are:",
            "options": [
                "Enzymes are bio catalysts.",
                "Enzymes are non-specific and cannot catalyse different kinds of reactions.",
                "Most enzymes are globular proteins.",
                "Enzyme - oxidase catalyses the hydrolysis of maltose into glucose."
            ],
            "correctOption": "Enzyme - oxidase catalyses the hydrolysis of maltose into glucose.",
            "id": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "The metal that cannot be obtained by electrolysis of an aqueous solution of its salt is",
            "options": [
                "Cr",
                "Ca",
                "Ag",
                "Cu"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Ca",
            "id": 27
        },
        {
            "question": "Which nitrogen compound does not give Lassaigne's test?",
            "options": [
                "Hydrazine",
                "Urea",
                "Glycene",
                "Phenyl Hydrazine"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Hydrazine",
            "id": 16
        },
        {
            "question": "Coagulation of egg on heating is because of:",
            "options": [
                "Denaturation of protein occurs.",
                "Biological properties of proteins remain unchanged",
                "Breaking of peptide linkage in the primary structure of protein occurs",
                "The secondary structure of protein remains unchanged"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Denaturation of protein occurs.",
            "id": 6
        },
        {
            "question": "Acidity of \u03b1-hydrogens of aldehydes and ketones is responsible for Aldol reaction. Benzaldehyde and ethanal will not give Cross-Aldol product.",
            "options": [
                "BOTH I AND II ARE TRUE",
                "BOTH I AND II ARE FALSE",
                "I IS TRUE BUT II IS FALSE",
                "II IS TRUE BUT I IS FALSE"
            ],
            "correctOption": "I IS TRUE BUT II IS FALSE",
            "id": 19
        },
        {
            "question": "Fusion of MnO2 with KOH and an oxidising agent gives dark green K2MnO4. Manganate ion on electrolytic oxidation in alkaline medium gives permanganate ion.",
            "options": [
                "BOTH I AND II ARE TRUE",
                "BOTH I AND II ARE FALSE",
                "I IS TRUE BUT II IS FALSE",
                "II IS TRUE BUT I IS FALSE"
            ],
            "correctOption": "II IS TRUE BUT I IS FALSE",
            "id": 5
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following has the highest number of unpaired electrons?",
            "options": [
                "Sc",
                "Cr",
                "V",
                "Ti"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Cr",
            "id": 7
        },
        {
            "question": "Which compound will not give silver mirror with ammoniacal AgNO3?",
            "options": [
                "Formic acid",
                "Formaldehyde",
                "Benzaldehyde",
                "Acetone"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Acetone",
            "id": 20
        },
        {
            "question": "Chlorine water on standing loses its colour and forms:",
            "options": [
                "HCl and HClO2",
                "HCl only",
                "HOCl and HOCl2",
                "HCl and HOCl"
            ],
            "correctOption": "HCl and HOCl",
            "id": 30
        },
        {
            "question": "The element having the highest first ionization enthalpy is",
            "options": [
                "C",
                "Al",
                "N",
                "Si"
            ],
            "correctOption": "N",
            "id": 39
        },
        {
            "question": "\u2206U is equal to",
            "options": [
                "adiabatic work",
                "isothermal work",
                "isochoric work",
                "isobaric work"
            ],
            "correctOption": "adiabatic work",
            "id": 33
        },
        {
            "question": "Kjeldahl method is applicable to pyridine. The nitrogen in pyridine can be converted to ammonium sulfate.",
            "options": [
                "BOTH I AND II ARE TRUE",
                "BOTH I AND II ARE FALSE",
                "II IS TRUE BUT I IS FALSE",
                "I IS TRUE BUT II IS FALSE"
            ],
            "correctOption": "BOTH I AND II ARE FALSE",
            "id": 17
        },
        {
            "question": "The gas liberated by the electrolysis of Dipotassium succinate solution is:",
            "options": [
                "Ethyne",
                "Propene",
                "Ethane",
                "Ethene"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Ethene",
            "id": 25
        },
        {
            "question": "The IUPAC name of CH3CHO is",
            "options": [
                "Acetaldehyde",
                "Ethanal",
                "Methyl aldehyde",
                "Ethanol"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Ethanal",
            "id": 22
        },
        {
            "question": "Haloalkanes react with KCN to form alkyl cyanides, but with AgCN form isocyanides. KCN and AgCN are highly ionic compounds.",
            "options": [
                "BOTH I AND II ARE TRUE",
                "BOTH I AND II ARE FALSE",
                "I IS TRUE BUT II IS FALSE",
                "II IS TRUE BUT I IS FALSE"
            ],
            "correctOption": "I IS TRUE BUT II IS FALSE",
            "id": 14
        },
        {
            "question": "The higher oxidation states are more stable down the group among transition elements unlike p-block elements. Copper cannot liberate hydrogen from weak acids.",
            "options": [
                "BOTH I AND II ARE TRUE",
                "BOTH I AND II ARE FALSE",
                "I IS TRUE BUT II IS FALSE",
                "II IS TRUE BUT I IS FALSE"
            ],
            "correctOption": "BOTH I AND II ARE TRUE",
            "id": 8
        },
        {
            "question": "The alkene that exhibits geometrical isomerism is:",
            "options": [
                "2\u2013methyl\u20132\u2013butene",
                "Propene",
                "2\u2013butene",
                "2\u2013methylpropene"
            ],
            "correctOption": "2\u2013butene",
            "id": 24
        },
        {
            "question": "The molecular formula of second homologue in the mono carboxylic acids series is:",
            "options": [
                "C2H2O4",
                "C2H2O2",
                "CH2O",
                "C3H6O2"
            ],
            "correctOption": "C2H2O4",
            "id": 18
        },
        {
            "question": "N(CH3)3 and P(CH3)3 can act as ligands. As N and P are from same group, the nature of bonding is always same with transition metals.",
            "options": [
                "BOTH I AND II ARE TRUE",
                "BOTH I AND II ARE FALSE",
                "I IS TRUE BUT II IS FALSE",
                "II IS TRUE BUT I IS FALSE"
            ],
            "correctOption": "I IS TRUE BUT II IS FALSE",
            "id": 9
        },
        {
            "question": "Phenol treated with chloroform in presence of sodium hydroxide, then hydrolyzed in acid results in:",
            "options": [
                "2-Hydroxybenzaldehyde",
                "Salicylic Acid",
                "quinol",
                "Benzene-1,2-diol"
            ],
            "correctOption": "2-Hydroxybenzaldehyde",
            "id": 11
        },
        {
            "question": "Common name of Benzene - 1,2 - diol is:",
            "options": [
                "o-cresol",
                "catechol",
                "quinol",
                "resorcinol"
            ],
            "correctOption": "catechol",
            "id": 12
        },
        {
            "question": "Time required for 99.9% completion of a first order reaction is _________ times the time required for 90% completion.",
            "options": [
                "1",
                "2",
                "3",
                "9"
            ],
            "correctOption": "3",
            "id": 4
        },
        {
            "question": "Which one of the following substances has the highest proton affinity?",
            "options": [
                "H2S",
                "NH3",
                "PH3",
                "H2O"
            ],
            "correctOption": "NH3",
            "id": 32
        },
        {
            "question": "The IUPAC name of CH3COCH(CH3)2 is",
            "options": [
                "3-methyl-2-butanone",
                "2-methyl-3-butanone",
                "4-methylisopropyl ketone",
                "Isopropylmethyl ketone"
            ],
            "correctOption": "3-methyl-2-butanone",
            "id": 21
        },
        {
            "question": "The incorrect postulates of the Dalton's atomic theory are:",
            "options": [
                "Atoms of different elements differ in mass.",
                "Matter consists of divisible atoms.",
                "Compounds are formed when atoms of different element combine in a fixed ratio.",
                "Chemical reactions involve reorganisation of atoms."
            ],
            "correctOption": "Matter consists of divisible atoms.",
            "id": 37
        },
        {
            "question": "Number of atoms in the following samples of substances is the largest in:",
            "options": [
                "127.0g of iodine",
                "48.0g of magnesium",
                "71.0g of chlorine",
                "4.0g of hydrogen"
            ],
            "correctOption": "4.0g of hydrogen",
            "id": 35
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What is the value of cos(0\u00c2\u00b0)?",
            "options": [
                "1",
                "0",
                "-1",
                "0.5"
            ],
            "correctOption": "1",
            "id": 4
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the volume of a sphere with radius r?",
            "options": [
                "(4/3)\u00cf\u20acr^3",
                "2\u00cf\u20acr^3",
                "\u00cf\u20acr^3",
                "(3/4)\u00cf\u20acr^3"
            ],
            "correctOption": "(4/3)\u00cf\u20acr^3",
            "id": 12
        },
        {
            "question": "Number of 4-digit numbers that are less than or equal to 2800 and either divisible by 3 or by 11 , is equal to ____________.",
            "options": [
                "990",
                "700",
                "710",
                "430"
            ],
            "correctOption": "710",
            "id": 49
        },
        {
            "question": "In a survey of 220 students... m and n respectively be the least and the most number of students who studied all the three subjects. Then m+n is equal to ___________.",
            "options": [
                "45",
                "20",
                "35",
                "50"
            ],
            "correctOption": "45",
            "id": 41
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the value of tan(45\u00c2\u00b0)?",
            "options": [
                "1",
                "0",
                "-1",
                "\u00e2\u02c6\u01612"
            ],
            "correctOption": "1",
            "id": 13
        },
        {
            "question": "The number of solutions of sin3x = cos 2x, in the interval (90,180) is :",
            "options": [
                "4",
                "7",
                "3",
                "1"
            ],
            "correctOption": "1",
            "id": 55
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the solution to the equation 2x + 3 = 7?",
            "options": [
                "x = 2",
                "x = 3",
                "x = 4",
                "x = 1"
            ],
            "correctOption": "x = 2",
            "id": 5
        },
        {
            "question": "The number of solutions of the equation x + 2tanx = \u03c0/2 in the interval [0, 2\u03c0] is :",
            "options": [
                "9",
                "7",
                "3",
                "4"
            ],
            "correctOption": "3",
            "id": 34
        },
        {
            "question": "The number of integers between 100 and 1000 having the sum of their digits equals to 14 , is _________",
            "options": [
                "45",
                "70",
                "35",
                "43"
            ],
            "correctOption": "70",
            "id": 27
        },
        {
            "question": "Let S = {1, 2, 3, 5, 7, 10, 11}. The number of non-empty subsets of S that have the sum of all elements a multiple of 3, is _____________.",
            "options": [
                "45",
                "20",
                "35",
                "43"
            ],
            "correctOption": "43",
            "id": 45
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the integral of 2x dx?",
            "options": [
                "x^2 + C",
                "2x + C",
                "x^2",
                "2x"
            ],
            "correctOption": "x^2 + C",
            "id": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the derivative of x^2?",
            "options": [
                "2x",
                "x^2",
                "x",
                "2"
            ],
            "correctOption": "2x",
            "id": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the derivative of sin(x)?",
            "options": [
                "cos(x)",
                "-sin(x)",
                "-cos(x)",
                "sin(x)"
            ],
            "correctOption": "cos(x)",
            "id": 19
        },
        {
            "question": "The number of solutions of the equation x + 2tanx = \u03c0/2 in the interval [0, 2\u03c0] is :",
            "options": [
                "9",
                "7",
                "3",
                "4"
            ],
            "correctOption": "3",
            "id": 54
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the sum of the first n natural numbers?",
            "options": [
                "n(n+1)/2",
                "n^2",
                "n(n-1)/2",
                "n^2 + n"
            ],
            "correctOption": "n(n+1)/2",
            "id": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "Let f(x) be a quadratic polynomial such that f(-2) + f(3) = 0. If one of the roots of f(x) = 0 is 1, then the sum of the roots of f(x) = 0 is equal to:",
            "options": [
                "3",
                "13/3",
                "35/3",
                "11/3"
            ],
            "correctOption": "11/3",
            "id": 50
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the value of e^0?",
            "options": [
                "1",
                "0",
                "e",
                "-1"
            ],
            "correctOption": "1",
            "id": 9
        },
        {
            "question": "If sin A + cos A = \u00bd , then 16(sin(2A) + cos(4A) + sin(6A)) is equal to :",
            "options": [
                "45",
                "-23",
                "35",
                "43"
            ],
            "correctOption": "-23",
            "id": 32
        },
        {
            "question": "The equation y = sinx sin (x + 2) \u2013 sin^2 (x + 1) represents a straight line lying in :",
            "options": [
                "III and IV QUADRANTS",
                "II and IV QUADRANTS",
                "I, III and IV QUADRANTS",
                "II,III and IV QUADRANTS"
            ],
            "correctOption": "III and IV QUADRANTS",
            "id": 53
        },
        {
            "question": "The number of relations... which are reflexive and transitive but not symmetric, is __________.",
            "options": [
                "1",
                "2",
                "3",
                "5"
            ],
            "correctOption": "3",
            "id": 44
        },
        {
            "question": "Let the circumcentre of a triangle with vertices A(a, 3), B(b, 5) and C(a, b)... x+y is equal to :",
            "options": [
                "4/7",
                "1/7",
                "8/7",
                "5/7"
            ],
            "correctOption": "4/7",
            "id": 38
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the sum of the angles in a triangle?",
            "options": [
                "180\u00c2\u00b0",
                "360\u00c2\u00b0",
                "90\u00c2\u00b0",
                "270\u00c2\u00b0"
            ],
            "correctOption": "180\u00c2\u00b0",
            "id": 7
        },
        {
            "question": "a = sin36 is a root of which of the following equation?",
            "options": [
                "16x^4-20x^2+5=0",
                "16x^4+20x^2+5=0",
                "16x^4-20x^2-5=0",
                "16x^4+20x^2-5=0"
            ],
            "correctOption": "16x^4-20x^2+5=0",
            "id": 51
        },
        {
            "question": "In a survey of 220 students... m and n respectively be the least and the most number of students who studied all the three subjects. Then m+n is equal to ___________.",
            "options": [
                "45",
                "20",
                "35",
                "50"
            ],
            "correctOption": "45",
            "id": 21
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the integral of cos(x) dx?",
            "options": [
                "sin(x) + C",
                "-cos(x) + C",
                "-sin(x) + C",
                "cos(x) + C"
            ],
            "correctOption": "sin(x) + C",
            "id": 20
        },
        {
            "question": "The number of integers between 100 and 1000 having the sum of their digits equals to 14 , is _________",
            "options": [
                "45",
                "70",
                "35",
                "43"
            ],
            "correctOption": "70",
            "id": 47
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the value of log10(100)?",
            "options": [
                "2",
                "1",
                "10",
                "100"
            ],
            "correctOption": "2",
            "id": 6
        },
        {
            "question": "A software company sets up m number of computer systems... then it took 8 more days to finish the assignment. The value of m is equal to:",
            "options": [
                "150",
                "220",
                "135",
                "250"
            ],
            "correctOption": "150",
            "id": 23
        },
        {
            "question": "If z = x + iy satisfies |z| - 2 = 0 and |z - i| - |z + 5i| = 0, then :",
            "options": [
                "x+2y+4=0",
                "x+2y-4=0",
                "x-2y+4=0",
                "x-2y-4=0"
            ],
            "correctOption": "x+2y+4=0",
            "id": 26
        },
        {
            "question": "a = sin36 is a root of which of the following equation?",
            "options": [
                "16x^4-20x^2+5=0",
                "16x^4+20x^2+5=0",
                "16x^4-20x^2-5=0",
                "16x^4+20x^2-5=0"
            ],
            "correctOption": "16x^4-20x^2+5=0",
            "id": 31
        }
    ]
]